Y A on Y A censored supernatural Bible
tunes on YouTube. And today is the 12th
of January 2024. If you have not yet
seen or read this, you're going to want
to go ahead and bookmark it. I will put
the tab I will put the link in the video
description below.
This is the new order of barbarians.
It's a transcript that I'm showing you
of three tapes on the new order of
barbarians. It referred to
on the tape simply as a new world
system. The first two tapes were
recorded 1988 and are the recollections
of Dr. Lawrence Dunegan
regarding a lecture he attended on March
20th, 1969
at a meeting of the Pittsburgh Pediatric
Society.
The lecture at the gathering of
pediatricians was Dr. Richard Day. He
died in 1989.
At the time, Dr. Day was a professor of
pediatrics at Mount Sinai Medical School
in New York. And previously he had
served as a medical director of Planned
Parenthood Federation of America.
Dr. Dunegan was formerly a student of
Dr. Day at the University of Pittsburgh
and is well acquainted with him although
not intimately. And he describes Dr. Day
as an insider of the order. And although
Dr. Dunegan's memory was somewhat dimmed
by the intervening years, he is able to
provide enough details of the lecture to
enable any enlightened person to discern
the real purposes behind the trends of
our time.
This is a transcript of a loose
conversational monologue that makes for
better listening than reading.
But you can find this on YouTube. But I
want to show you
this is really interesting and it is
related to the Bible changes. So this is
a very long
very long interview as you can see
covering all types of really
interesting, relevant
events that are happening today. But
especially I want to talk to you about
this. Um actually I'm going to scroll
down to it.
Um let's see if I can find it. Sorry
about this. I can't do a quick find on
this, so I'm going to have to scroll
down here.
But on in this interview, he talks about
the blending of religions. And I'm
actually going to read it for you here.
Another area of discussion was religion.
This is an avowed atheist speaking, and
he said, "Religion is not necessarily
bad.
A lot of people seem to need religion
with its mysteries and rituals,
so they will have religion. But the
major religions of today have to be
changed because they're not compatible
with the change to come.
The old religions will have to go,
especially Christianity.
Once the Roman Catholic Church is
brought down, the rest of Christianity
will follow easily. Then a new religion
can be accepted for use all over the
world. It will incorporate something
from all of the old ones to make it more
easy for people to accept it and feel at
home in it. Most people won't be too
concerned with religion. They will
realize that they don't need it.
And the next topic says, "Changing the
Bible through revisions of key words."
In order to do this, the Bible will be
changed. It will be rewritten to fit the
new religion. Gradually, key words will
replace the new words having various
shades of meaning.
Then the meaning attached to the new
word can be close to the old world word.
And as time goes on, other shades of
meaning of that word can be emphasized.
And then gradually, that word replaced
with another word.
I don't know if I'm making that clear,
but the idea is that everything in
scripture needs not be rewritten.
Just key words replaced by other words,
and the variability in meaning attached
to any word can be used as a tool to
change the entire meaning of scripture
and therefore make it acceptable to this
new religion.
Most people won't know the difference,
and this was another one of the times
when he He "The few
who do notice a change won't be enough
to matter."
Pretty crazy, is it not?
Are we not seeing that happen
right now?
So, again, I will link this article in
the video description below.
Definitely take a look, save it, and
share it.
It's all right here.
They told us what they were going to do,
but more importantly, really the Bible
told us what was going to happen.
And yet,
still
so many people resist the truth,
embracing the new satanic language and
imagery that's in Bible in the Bible.
And what were they?
Be strong, courageous brothers and
sisters. Do not fear or be dismayed, for
the Lord your God is with you wherever
you go. Until next time.